(COMPUTER DINGS)
Ooh! I got one, too.
(Stuart:)The ladies are coming to us.
(Stuart:)Oh, man,
if I'd started this years ago,
(Stuart:)I'd be divorced two or three times
by now.
(COMPUTER CHIMES)
(Raj:)What...? Another one.
You know, ifs weird.
(Raj:)When they're reading your profile,
does it make you feel exposed?
(Raj:)Like they see you naked?
(Stuart:)Well, they're not running away
screaming, so, no.
(Amy:)I love Little House.
(Amy:)It made me want to live
on a farm so much.
(Amy:)I tried to milk my cat.
(Amy:)That tangy bowl of Cheerios
was not worth the stitches.
(Sheldon:)Well, you sit back, relax,
(Sheldon:)and enjoy a beloved
childhood memory.
J' (LITTLE HOUSE ON THE PRAIRIE
THEME PLAYS) J'
(Sheldon:)You see that cabin there?